

ADI IRFAN SAFRUDIN WEB DEVELOPER

MALANG, 30 APRIL 1996 Perumahan Bukit Pamulang indah blok A3 no 6 Pamulang, Tangsel



ABOUT ME

Adi Irfan Safrudin, mostly called Adi, is a the last childs of 2 brothers, born and grown up in Malang,he is currently living at South Tangerang,and curently working as a Web Developer, Used goods seller, and freelancer. Has 4 years experience as Web Developer, most work as a FullStack web developer, but currently focusing on become Front End Engineer,



WORK EXPERIENCE

LYTO DATARINDO FORTUNA JULY 2018 - NOW | WEB DEVELOPER

Responsible for developing website, and adding some features in existed website, language program used: HTML5, CSS (SCSS), jS(Vue. js, jQuery), PHP and

AKABE TECH | MAY 2017 - JULY 2018 | LEAD WEB DEVELOPER

Responsible to developing Web Apps called BeLaundry, maintenance Web Services and API, manage team peformance to fit the target, also contribute new feature to meet the requirement from client

CLOUDARON PTE LTD | JAN 2016 - FEB 2017 | SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Main task is to developing Web Apps called Education Cloud, and also developing Website P2P lending platform called kredito

PT AIVON MEDIATAMA | MAY 2014 - DECEMBER 2015 | WEB DEVELOPER

Responsible to developing website and also maintenance current existed code,make a monthly report from google analytic, and monthly newsletter blasting



SKILLS

HTML CSS JS PHP



MYSQL

PERSONAL SKILLS

PROBLEM SOLVE -**TEAM WORK LEARNING** INNOVATE



LANGUAGE

BAHASA ENGLISH



EDUCATION

BUDI LUHUR UNIVERSITY 2015 - NOW

Majoring in System Information

SMK TELKOM SANDHY PUTRA MALANG | 2011 - 2014

Majoring in Networking

MIKROTIK ACADEMY 2014

CISCO CCNA ACADEMY 2014



081388640320





github.com/adiirfan adiirfan01@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/adi-irfan01 my.adiirfan.tech





ADDITIONAL SKILL

- 1. CSS Preprocessor
- 2. Vue.jS
- 3. npm / yarn package manager
- 4. git
- 5. Firebase
- 6. Bootstrap, Bulma, Materialize
- 7. Codelgniter
- 8. Laravel
- 9. Lumen
- 10.CLI
- 11. HTTP Request
- 12. Express JS
- 13. Web Services/API

PORTOFOLIO





















